

UX DESIGNER I FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT



ADDRESS

Sunnistajankuja 6 b 29 Vantaa, Finland



DATE OF BIRTH

11. 12.1995



MOBILE

+358451975104



E-MAIL

umerghafour@gmail.com



WEBISTE

www.omerg.fi



Linked in

https://linkedin.com/in/matinghafouromer

LANGUAGES









PROFILE

I'm twenty-three (22) years young passionate technologist based in Helsinki, studying business information technology at Haaga-Helia university. I have over three years of experience in field of ICT web development and system support on various environments and platforms for data driven web, desktop. My background includes development in a team of multinational system administrators, software testers, and support quality controllers

SKILLS



EDUCATION

2016 - 2018

Haaga-Helia University of applied sciences

BACHELOR DEGREE - BUSINESS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY MAJORING IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING / DIGITAL SERVICES.

2014 - 2016

HELSINKI VOCATIONAL COLLEGE

Technical college degree in data and communication technology -ICT Technician

WORK EXPERIENCE

12.2016-3.2017

UX DESIGNER- ENPSE GROUP OY

- Design develop, prototypeing, wireframe usability of software products.
- Developed user personas and scenarios in order to enhance functionality and usability for key audiences.
- · Gathered requirements from clients and conducted focus group to discover user needs.

6.2016-8.2016

ICT CUSTOMER SERVICE **HELSINGIN CITY OFFICE (CITY LIBRARY)**

- Working with customers/employees to identify computer problems and advising on the solution
- · Logging and keeping records of customer/employee queries
- Analysing call logs so you can spot common trends and underlying problems
- Updating self-help documents so customers/employees can try to fix probelem themselves

1.2014-7.2014

APPLICATION TESTER -STUDENT WORK

- Participating in preparing Test Plans.
- Preparing Suggestion Documents to improve the quality.
- Set up the required test beds (hardware, software and network)
- Procure or create test data required for testing.
- Test software releases by executing assigned tests (manual)
- Create test logs & Offline/Online data collection capabilities